We've even learned some advanced sections of solidity.
我们甚至学习完了 Solidity 的一些进阶内容
And this is going to be the last time that we start our projects in remix,
但这将是我们最后一次在 Remix 中打开我们的项目
we're going to be moving over to a code editor now,
现在我们要转而使用代码编辑器了
where we can get even more advanced with our solidity on our setups.
在那里我们可以获得更多 Solidity 的高级设置
For the most part, you've gone over the vast majority of solidity basics,
为了应对大多数情况，你已经学习了绝大多数 Solidity 的基础知识
there are a number of things that we still haven't learned yet.
这里还有一些我们没有学到的东西
And the reason we haven't gotten into them is because they get more advanced.
没有深入研究这些内容的原因是它们的用法比较高级
And understanding the real use doesn't really make too much sense until a little bit later.
稍晚一些再了解它们的用途会更有意义
Some of the things that we're going to go over are
要讲的其中一些东西的是
itams events, try catch function selectors,
枚举(Enum)，事件(Events)，Try Catch，函数选择器(Function Selector)
abi encoding, hashing, and then you will slash and then you will slash assembly.
abi 编码(encode)，哈希(Hashing)，以及 Yul / Assembly
However, if you've gotten this far,
不过既然已经走到了这么远
you probably can read most solidity code and understand what's going on,
你大概已经可以阅读大多数 Solidity 代码并理解其中的意思了
which is absolutely fantastic.
这简直棒极了
So you should give yourself a huge round of applause for getting this far. And doing this.
所以你应该为自己能走到这一步而鼓掌
Let's do a quick summary of this more advanced section
让我们快速总结一下这些进阶内容
and make sure we understand what we learned
确保我们理解了所学的内容
in solidity there are a couple special functions.
在 Solidity 中有一些特殊函数
Some of them are receive fallback, and Constructor.
其中几个是 receive fallback 和 constructor
These functions don't need to have the function keyword. And instead it can just be called like so.
这些函数不需要 function 关键字，而是只能这样调用
Receive and fallback are two very special functions.
receive 和 fallback 是两个非常特殊的函数
If data is sent with a transaction, and no function was specified,
如果 data 通过交易发送过来，且没有指定任何函数
the transaction will default to the fallback function if that fallback function exists.
交易将默认执行 fallback 函数，如果 fallback 函数存在的话
If data is empty, and there's a receive function,
如果 data 为空，并且存在 receive 函数，
it'll call the receive function.
就会调用 receive 函数
There are a couple of keywords that can help us save gas in the long run.
从长远来看，有几个关键字可以帮助我们节约 gas
Some of those keywords are going to be constant and immutable.
其中两个就是 constant 和 immutable
Constant and immutable are for variables that can only be declared and updated once.
constant 和 immutable 针对的是只能声明和更新一次的变量
Once we say minimum USD is 50 times 118.
当我们说 MINIMUM_USD 是 50 乘以 1e18 时
This minimum USD can never be changed again.
这个 MINIMUM_USD 就不能再被改变了
And this helps us save gas.
这有助于我们节省 gas
Immutable can also save gas similar to constant.
immutable 也可以像 constant 一样节省 gas
However, immutable variables can be declared one time in the constructor,
然而，immutable 变量可以在 constructor 中改变一次
once an immutable variable is declared, it can't be changed later on.
一旦一个 immutable 变量被声明出来，以后就不能再改变了
In fact, if we even tried to update an immutable variable or constant variable, and we compiled,
事实上，如果我们试图更新 immutable 变量或者 constant 变量，然后编译它
a compiler would give us an error saying, Can't write to a mutable here.
编译器会抛出一个错误说，不能在此处写入 immutable 变量
Or if we tried to change a constant variable.
或者我们可以尝试修改一个 constant 变量
Our compiler would say, Hey, you can't assign to a constant variable, sorry.
我们的编译器会说，嘿，你不能给一个 constant 变量赋值，抱歉
In remix, if we want to send ether to a contract that's on the JavaScript virtual machine,
在 Remix 中如果我们想给一个在 JavaScript 虚拟机上的合约发送以太币
we can deploy that contract.
我们可以部署这个合约
And then in the contract, we can just hit the transact button without any call data
然后在这个合约里，我们可以只是点击这个 Transact 按钮而不发送任何 CALLDATA
and update the value that we send with the transaction.
并更新我们通过交易发送的价值
If call data is blank, it will trigger the receive function if it exists.
如果 CALLDATA 为空，它就会触发 receive 函数，如果存在的话
But if there's data that doesn't specify any of the other functions,
但如果这里有数据却没有指定任何一个函数的话
it'll trigger the fallback function
它就会触发 fallback 函数